[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
Mr. Paterno's dead.
We need to be cautious.
I'm not dealing with just anybody.
But I got a lead. Mercedes Palacio.
[Damian] These people are
on a different level.
She can't win this.
I know you're worried for my daughter,
but you have to trust her.
[Damian] Camia, you need to fear them
because Lily's already
standing in her own grave.
-[Anna] I saw Arnaldo.
-[Jepoy] Arnaldo?
[Anna] He didn't do anything to me.
Actually, it seems like he's changed.
[Jepoy] A snake may shed
its skin but it's still a snake.
-You bastard!
-[grunts]
-Why'd you hurt Anna?
-I don't--
-What did I ever do to you?
-I don't know you!
Why do you keep hurting the people I love?
I was about to get rid of Arnaldo
when he got in the way.
[Lily] We are not murderers.
If you kill even just
one of the Ardientes,
we will forever have their blood
smeared on our hands and conscience.
[Arnaldo] I won't come with you.
I won't be safer with any of you.
What do you mean?
I found out about your crimes, Grandpa.
-Are you even my grandson?!
-[Raul] Papa!
And, if you don't stop
harassing the Ardientes,
I assure you, your loved ones
will be in grave danger.
I've been to hell and back.
So there's no way
I'll ever be afraid of you.
What is this?
I believe that at least
one of you Ardientes
had something to do with
the bombings of my businesses.
[Mercedes] Emilia, the time has come.
Your real mother wants to see you.
[Emilia] Mama?
[Helena] Emilia, my daughter.
[sobbing]
[Emilia continues sobbing]
Mama…
I've waited all these years.
Not longer than I've waited, Emilia.
But I… I just want to ask you.
Why did you abandon me?
Why, Mama? I want to understand.
Why did you leave me? [sobs]
I did not abandon you, Emilia.
Then why is it that all these years,
they made me believe
that the woman who raised me
was my mother, not you?
Why did you only show up now?
Emilia, please don't blame me.
Don't doubt me.
[sobs]
I was a victim too, just like you.
Somehow, I find it difficult
to believe that, Mama.
Your father took you away from me, Emilia.
Emilia, please believe me.
All these years,
I thought that I lost you.
[sobbing]
You'll know the truth when your
father and I meet again soon.
[whimpering]
I want it to come straight from him…
as to how and why he broke us apart.
Emilia, darling…
I want him to admit
the horrible thing he did to us.
[sobs] Mama…
Mama!
[sobbing]
[Emilia continues sobbing]
My Mama… [sobs]
Mama…
[sobbing]
[pensive music playing]
[pensive music continues]
Where did this come from?!
Who received this?!
You didn't even check what was inside!
What if it was a bomb? I could've died!
We're sorry, boss.
We didn't quite catch the woman
who left it at the gate.
So, you didn't even know
who that woman was,
and yet you accepted the gift?!
You want some of this, huh?
You want this?! There!
Well?! Don't just stand there!
Clean up those filthy maggots!
[tense music playing]
Chief De Dios, this is Miss Cruz.
Miss Cruz. Have a seat, ma'am.
Myla's jail transfer has been approved.
We're just waiting for updates.
Sir! Sir!
-Why?
-We need to call the medic.
-What happened?
-Myla Lomeda was stabbed.
[tense music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
[Helena] Come here, darling.
Mercedes, bring out all the jewelry.
It's my surprise for you!
Oh my gosh, Mama! Are these all for me?
Yes, and you deserve more!
Wow!
But, Mama…
None of these gifts
will solve my problems.
Why, darling? What's wrong?
Tell me about it and I will help you.
I actually have three problems, Mama.
Number one is Lily Cruz.
She always wants to take me
and my family down.
Number two is Papa.
He never gives me the
opportunity to rise to power.
He always wants everything
for himself. He's selfish.
[sighs]
And what is the third problem?
It's, um…
about my love life, Mama.
And it's too personal.
[sighs] Don't worry, I'll help you.
I'll go to Poblacion Ardiente.
And I will eliminate both
your Papa and Lily Cruz.
I'll give you back your crown
and you will be the queen of Ardiente.
Oh my god, Mama!
You are the best!
I love you so much, Mama.
[Emilia chuckles]
[somber music playing]
Myla…
Myla, don't worry. You're safe here.
No one can just come in here.
I might be safe but I'm sure
my family's in danger.
You can tell me where your family is.
I'll have them picked up.
Thank you.
I didn't think they could do this to me…
after how loyal I was to them.
That's why we should
help each other, Myla.
Tell me where I can find Mercedes…
so I can silence her.
But, Mama, I just wanted to ask you…
How'd you do that?
Lily Cruz is no pushover,
and Papa is a very powerful man.
[exhales] Believe me, darling.
They are amateurs compared to me.
[sighs] I was just wondering, Mama.
Who are you, really?
How did you clear my case?
How did you talk Mateo into
getting me as his consultant?
And about Aguas Realty, how did
you bomb all their properties?
How'd you do that, Mama?
How did you become this rich and powerful?
[ominous music playing]
[Myla] Even if you find Mercedes,
none of this will end.
Because Mercedes
isn't even the real boss here.
Myla, if that's true, who's
the mastermind behind all this?
You have to help me.
We need to help each other.
Who is behind all of this, Myla?
Red Dragon.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music swells]
[foreboding music playing]
Lily?
[Lily sighs]
Mercedes Palacio isn't my real enemy.
It's Red Dragon.
Red Dragon?
No one knows Red Dragon's
identity or what she looks like.
But from what I was told,
she controls all the syndicates.
Be it drugs, robbery, terrorism…
They all answer to Red Dragon.
Compared to her,
Emilia and Julio are nothing.
The question is…
What's Red Dragon's connection
to Emilia and the Ardientes?
[foreboding music playing]
They call me Red Dragon,
"queen of the underworld."
I hold politicians
and the law by the neck.
But that is all you need to know for now.
The important thing is, my dear daughter,
we will never, ever be apart.
[somber music playing]
[Lily] Red Dragon
is the head of the biggest
prostitution, smuggling,
white slavery, kidnap-for-ransom,
and terrorist syndicate
in the Philippines.
But I just can't understand
why she'd come after me.
Her second-in-command? Mercedes Palacio.
She used to work with Mr. Paterno,
and ordered Myla Lomeda
to bomb the condominiums,
media complex,
and the Aguas Realty building.
So it's Mercedes Palacio who carries out
all of Red Dragon's orders?
Yes. Mercedes Palacio is
our link to Red Dragon.
That is, if we find her.
But I'm sure I will.
[tense music playing]
[somber music playing]
[Julio] Have you really come back?
Why?
Why now?
[somber music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
That business is under
Mercedes Palacio's name.
Club Dragon Fly.
If my hunch is right,
we'll find Red Dragon there.
Whoever that Red Dragon is,
I will make sure I find her.
I hope she's ready.
[tense music playing]
[somber music playing]
[clicks tongue, sighs]
That Julio…
Now that I've found you, Emilia…
I promise you,
no one and nothing is going
to separate us ever again.
And if anyone tries, I will crush them.
[scoffs] And that Papa of yours?
He's going to get what he deserves.
[foreboding music playing]
[foreboding music swells]
[Anna] All right, please put those
in the car.
Let's go.
-Anna, we'll go ahead.
-All right.
See you guys tomorrow. Take care.
Ma'am, here's the assignment…
Thank you very much for everything.
We'll just come back tomorrow
for the kids.
All right. Thank you.
Let me help you with that.
Looks like the kids really wore you out.
I didn't get your name the other day.
I'm Arnaldo, by the way.
[soft music playing]
-Jepoy!
-Wait, wait, wait!
-Jepoy, wait!
-Stay away from her!
Why are you always following her?!
Just try going near her and I'll kill you!
-Jepoy, stop it.
-Peace be with you.
Just drop the act, will you?!
No one's going to believe you,
you murderer!
I might as well just kill you
while your brother's not here!
[Anna] Jepoy!
-Stop it, Jepoy.
-You're tough, right?
-You're an Ardiente, right?
-Jepoy, would you stop that?
Anna, don't protect that bastard!
Anna, he'll kill you
if he gets the chance.
But he wasn't fighting back!
He wasn't, right?
Jepoy, we already talked about this.
Anna, are you really that gullible?
Don't let that liar fool you.
He's a murderer.
He killed Aunt Carlotta.
Go home and I'll finish him off
once and for all.
Hold up, Jepoy. You're the one
who's keeping secrets here.
You're the traitor.
You're the one
who's not telling the truth.
Anna, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Jepoy, stop playing dumb.
Why are you always outside day and night?
Who are you going to?
Are you betraying us now, Jepoy?
Why can't you answer me?
Spit it out! What are you up to?
You don't know what you're talking about.
Stay out of my business.
Do you understand?
Stop it, Jepoy.
Whatever you're doing, just stop it.
That's only going to lead you to trouble.
You don't know anything, Anna.
You don't know what I'm going through.
I guess you don't need me here anymore.
Jepoy.
Anna.
Are you okay?
[sighs]
Thank you for trusting me.
Sorry about that.
[pensive music playing]
-Madam.
-Mercedes, look.
I finally met my daughter.
Isn't she delightful? She's so pretty.
She looks as beautiful as you, Madam.
-Thank you.
-I hope, though,
that you didn't provide her a copy
as she might post it
on her social media accounts.
Don't worry, Mercedes.
She does not have a copy.
[soft thud]
[stomping]
There. Evidence gone.
I just wanted to feel
how a mother would normally feel
even for a few minutes.
Rest assured, I won't be careless,
especially now that
I've already met my daughter.
I need to utilize all my power
to be able to eliminate Emilia's enemies.
Prepare for war, Mercedes.
We will spare neither Julio nor Lily Cruz.
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
We'll follow that car.
Follow that car. Now.
[tense music playing]
[club music playing]
[applauding]
Hey, why are you still here? Hurry up!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
The show's about to start! Hurry! Go!
Let's give them
a good show, girls! We're late!
Boys, what are you doing? Hurry up!
Come on! Come on! Do your best!
Okay, let's go! Do your best!
Excuse me! You two!
Yeah, you two! Come here!
Were you sent by Jennifer?
Uh…
-Yeah, Jennifer.
-[Madonna] Come here.
-That's us.
-Come on, hurry. Get changed.
The show's about to start.
This one's yours.
Hurry up! You need to look great.
This is gonna be a great show.
Come on. Come on, hurry.
This way, this way. Get dressed, hurry.
[club music playing in distance]
-We'll just get dressed.
-Okay, go. Go.
[club music playing]
[Madonna] Raffy, drinks, please.
Thank you.
[sensual music playing]
[sensual music continues]
Oh no.
Good grief.
Looks like they didn't even practice.
[exasperated sigh]
[sensual music continues]
In fairness to them, they caught up.
Very good.
[crowd applauding]
[sensual music continues]
Madonna.
Oh! [chuckles]
Hello, Boss Apollo!
You're looking very handsome today!
You're so cute! [giggles]
You're as cute as ever! So handsome!
Who's that?
Is she new?
Uh, actually, sir,
my best friend just asked me
to take them in.
And you know how helpful
and charitable I am to everyone.
So, um… I included them here.
But look at them!
They're terrifically perfect.
Aren't they amazing?
I only asked you one question.
You said too much.
Uh…
Why are you letting strangers
into my club?
Your club? But you're just
the manager here.
This is Red Dragon's club.
-What did you say?
-Oh, sorry. I was just kidding!
[laughing] That's not what I mean, sir.
Bring her to the VIP room later.
I want to meet her.
Sure, sir. I will.
[chuckling]
Love you, sir. [chuckles sarcastically]
[sensual music continues]
[ominous music playing]
[crowd applauding]
[somber music playing]
I'm asking you. Who are you meeting?
The governor.
So with Papa having been
unseated as the governor,
I'll just prove my worth
that I can still be the queen.
Now that you're working
for this Mateo Ruiz…
[scoffs] What is it
that you want me to do, Papa?
Men are like dogs.
[mimics barking]
A little caress here and there,
and they're all yours.
You're a very attractive woman.
I'm sure he'll give in to you.
Did something happen between you?
Raul, I can't believe you!
If he has a hidden agenda,
that's not my problem anymore!
[Raul] Yes, it is!
That should be your concern
because we're married!
Just because I let that thing
between you and Jaguar slide…
What?
Now you've got another guy lined up?
You checked my phone, didn't you?
I'm changing my password right now!
If you aren't guilty,
you wouldn't do that!
What is it you admire
about that governor, anyway?
He's just Lily Cruz's lapdog, isn't he?
That's what you think.
What you don't know is that
Governor Ruiz has a new master.
And you're in front of her.
Bye, Kitty-kitty!
Meow!
Oops, I'm sorry. Jaguar, bye-bye!
[tense music playing]
[exhales]
[inaudible]
Apollo.
[ominous music plays]
Madam, welcome to paradise.
-Your paradise, not mine.
-[thwacks]
[tense music playing]
You're turning my club
into your personal playground.
I'm doing my job properly, Madam.
I love my job.
You know me, Apollo.
I do not tolerate incompetence.
Fail me just once… and you're out.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia humming]
[chuckles] You look happy tonight.
Why? Did I violate something?
Is there a law against humming?
No, but when it comes to your
obligations to me as my wife,
that's where we have a problem.
And how did this conversation
lead to that?
Because after 20 years of our marriage,
this is the first time
I've seen you this happy.
Why? Is it wrong to be this happy?
You're blooming tonight.
Did someone hit a home run?
What did you say?! You're disgusting.
-Disgusting, huh?
-[gasps]
[Emilia shrieking]
-Raul, stop it!
-Hold on.
Hey! You have your obligations
to me as my wife!
Stop it! This is wrong--
I'm not in the mood!
What's wrong with you?!
Emilia!
[panting]
[sensual music playing]
[chuckles]
This way, sir.
[tense music playing]
Looks like Red Dragon's here.
Let's follow them. Keep your eyes peeled.
[tense music playing]
[inaudible]
Who are you?
[Lily] Uh…
Um, we're new here.
We just got off the stage.
We're performers.
Um…
I need to use the ladies' room.
Do you know where that is?
There's no restroom here, miss.
It's downstairs.
Um…
Are you performers too?
We're waiting for customers.
They'll call us when someone
wants to take us out--
Shush! Don't tell her that!
We'll get in trouble if anyone finds out.
But she seems nice. We're friends, right?
How old are you?
-Seventeen.
-I'm sixteen.
I'm seventeen.
Oh.
[whispers] Lily, we have to go.
Someone's coming.
Let's go. Come on.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Hello, Madrigal?
Well, I just wanted to say
that I need you now.
So, come to me… now.
Wow. You talk like you
own me or something.
I'm not your lapdog.
I'm paying you.
And you owe me your life, remember?
Have you forgotten?
[sighs] Well, whether you like it or not,
I'm your master,
and you are my tempting and hot slave.
And I need to see you now.
Are you coming? For Mommy?
[exhales sharply]
[foreboding music playing]
That Red Dragon is the devil incarnate.
She's pimping underage girls?!
That woman is pure evil.
We'll come back for them.
But for now, we have to find out
who Red Dragon is.
[Madonna] There you are, girl!
Wait, did you go in there?
Oh, dear. You're not allowed here.
Anyway, honey, I've been looking for you.
The boss wants to see you in the VIP room.
Let's go.
Red Dragon is waiting.
Red Dragon will be there?
Come on, girl. We have to go.
You know, if you're lucky enough,
you'll be one of the few
who get to see her.
In all my years here,
I still haven't seen her myself.
But why?
Oh, honey, Red Dragon
is a very private person.
Only a few people know her.
And if things work out,
you might get to meet her.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music playing]
This is all the club has earned?
Well, there's nothing I can do
if customers don't come in
like they used to.
Ever since you were assigned here,
this club's income has decreased
by three percent every month.
You also have the lowest returns
out of all the clubs that Red Dragon owns.
And now you're saying
there's nothing you can do.
Do a better job!
But I am doing my job.
[foreboding music playing]
Is she the woman Boss Apollo requested?
Yes, she is.
Isn't she drop-dead gorgeous?
Look, um…
It seems like everyone's
a little tense here.
Why don't we…
Why don't we have fun and relax?
After all, that's the nature
of our business.
I'll go get us some food and drinks.
Come on in. They're waiting for you.
[fingers snap]
[unsettling music playing]
[woman] Where's Madam Red Dragon?
You just missed her.
[tense music playing]
Mercedes.
-Madam?
-Keep an eye on Apollo.
Make sure that he does what's necessary
to improve the security detail
and income of this club.
-Understood, Madam.
-Let's go.
I'm bored of this place.
Go on. Leave us.
[tense music playing]
Come here.
[suspenseful music playing]
Closer.
What's your name?
Call me whatever you want.
[tense music playing]
Looks like the girl is the boss' type.
-Has Red Dragon left?
-She's gone.
The boss has the girl to himself.
[scoffs] Poor girl.
[scoffs] Oh, well.
[tense music playing]
Nice.
That's what I like about women like you.
Good answer.
[tense music playing]
Feisty.
[foreboding music playing]
What are you doing here?
You're not allowed here!
[tense music playing]
But I think it would be better if…
if I were to see you without a mask.
[tense music playing]
[cop] This is the police!
[Lily] I know exactly what she's doing.
That's why I'll never trust that woman.
[Helena] That's what I want
to do to my new enemies.
Just like fire melts gold,
I want to burn Lily Cruz alive!
[Damian] You have no idea
how vicious your enemies are.
But I'm here.
I will protect you from Red Dragon,
even if it kills me.
[Helena] Pack your bags, Mercedes.
It's time for me
to meet the devil himself.
Hello, ex-lover.
-Helena.
-I'm back.
I am Red Dragon.
[theme music playing]